本字幕由 YYeTs人人影視 修正調整
歡迎愛好者加入我們 www.YYeTs.com
■
字幕來源：   影視帝國
字幕處理：~penny~  後期：~penny~
■
史提勒說  任何會吹大喇叭的女孩 都能做很多事
Any girI that knows how to play a tuba, she can do things. That's what stifler says
伊麗絲  你認為 麥特是自以為是的種馬...
Elyse, you think Matt is an arrogant Jock who wears his penis on his forehead...
我已煥然一新了 對了  你們兩個戴褲襪很好看喔
so I'm a totally new man, and.... By the way, you both look great in pantyhose
用右手   用右手 但我也可以用左手   用左手
With my right, with my right, but I can also do it with my left, with my left
-謝謝你把分數贏回來  -是我丟掉的  我得贏回來
-Thanks for winning those points back. -I lost them. I had to get them back
克洛依的事我聽了你的建議 用機器人送了一罐飲料過去
Hey, so, I took your advice about Chloe. I used the Rover to deliver a soda
是他的暱稱 他看到什麼都要插進去  不正常
Yeah, it's his nickname. Dude wilI stick his dick into anything. It's unnatural
用力點  喂  你這豬臉! 我真不知道該怎麼說你
Drive it in. Hey, you, fuck face, I don't even know where to start with you
那個蠢侏儒不是我們團裡的 我們對他的行為不負責任
That cretin is not in our band, and we are not responsible for his actions
-你要看我立刻肅立嗎?  -看過了  小意思
-You want to see me firmly at attention? -I already have. I wasn't impressed
這不是你的世界  是我們的 我們不要你加入
This isn't your world. This is our world, and we don't want you in it
今天下午議員們在排練才藝表演時...
so, this afternoon, while the counselors were practicing for the talent show...
羅伯茲需要有天份的音樂家 也需要有才幹的捐助人
Robards needs talented musicians as much as we need talented donors
-我是麥擴  負責處理...  -他在這裡幹什麼?
-I'm the Macro and it's my Job to deaI with... -What is he doing here?
藥草萃取可讓你們山毛櫸高校 同聲合吐哦!
This herbaI fucking extract wilI help you Beechwood fief play in tune, huh?
我才不關心他用相機偷拍我 我是說我不是不關心...
I don't even care that he saw me on camera. Well, I mean I do, but....
記住  我們將在畢業典禮儀式後演出
Remember, we play this at the end of the ceremony after Pomp and Circumstance
噢  那東西在我剛到時就在了 我想上面是你的名字
Oh, yeah, that was here when I arrived. I think it has your name on it
-有肛交協會?  -當然  但你得成為高手才行
-There's an AnaI sex Association? -Oh, yeah, but you've got to be a pro
我也拍不到好鏡頭 因為整個儀隊的人都討厭我
And I'm not getting any good footage 'cause these fucking bandees hate me
你午餐吃壞的吧? 我的胃也很敏感
you had for lunch, you know? I've got the same problem. Very sensitive stomach
如果你進了醫務室 珊德絲護士會照顧你
If you visit our infirmary, Nurse sanders wilI take care of your every need
小甜心  我只是好心警告你 羅伯茲獎學金是我的
I'm Just giving you fair warning, cupcake. Robards scholarship is mine
讓她喝醉? 這就是陳年大秘密嗎? 這就是第二步?
Get her drunk? That's the secret of the ages? That's step Number Two?
-麥特  請再選一題  -好吧  隨便
-Matt, Just pick another question, please. -AlI right, screw it. Whatever
貝多芬主要交響曲中 哪一首的第四樂章最長?
Of Beethoven's maJor symphonies, which has the longest fourth movement?
沒人告訴過你大人物在吃飯時 別去打擾他嗎?
Didn't anybody telI you not to mess with the big dog while he's eating?
麥特  我認為大家想要喜歡你 只是你沒讓事情容易些
I think people want to like you, Matt. You Just make it really hard
休士頓小姐  試聽很精彩 我們去談談獎學金的事吧
Excellent audition, Miss. Houston. Let's go discuss that scholarship
各位  畢業典禮儀式 將在五分鐘後開始  準備
Okay, everybody, Pomp and Circumstance. Five-minute warning. Let's go
他們不管贏過幾次 今天就是喝不到葡萄汁
I don't care how many times they won. They're not getting the grape today
這是脫衣問答遊戲  我們發明的 也是儀隊營的傳統
It's called strip Trivia. We made it up. It's a Band Camp tradition
我是銀色的史特拉第瓦裡喇叭 由普里茲獎得主吹奏
I am a silver stradivarius trumpet played by a Pulitzer Prize winner
就像我們還小時 在我旁邊你就是普通的麥特...
Just like when we were kids, around me, you were regular old Matt...
我們卻完全沒機會展露頭角 真是爛透了
and we ain't got no prospects for our palm pilots. That's fucked up, dawg
還是她的原始需求能被滿足 然後把他當作晚餐呢?
or wilI she satisfy her primaI needs and then devour him for dinner?
做點愛情樂曲吧 然後音符就會自動浮現了
Make some love music, you know? And then your notes wilI Just cum to you
對  他有夠嫩的 年紀都這麼大了還這麼嫩
Yeah, he's a preemie. I'm not talking about the day he was born, either
議長先生  那他們是誰? 第一夫人和副藝妓嗎?
Oh, and who are they, Mr. President? The First Lady and Vice Pussy?
跟你所習慣的相同 像在橄欖球隊裡...
something you're familiar with, being on the footbalI team, I'm sure...
-搞砸了我們的畢業典禮  -我去那裡玩友誼賽...
-and ruined our graduation. -I went there for a friendly game....
親愛的  請原諒我的用語 這樣說跟事實夠接近了嗎?
Excuse the expression, dear. ls that close to being on the money?
嘿  我只是想謝謝你們叫我起床 你們真好
Hey, I Just want to say thanks for the little wakeup call. You kidders
有一次我參加餐宴 真不敢相信  他們把...
I was at a banquet once. On the same plate, if you can believe it...
-你在這裡幹嘛  麥特?  -我來祝你好運
-What're you doing here, Matt? -I Just came by to wish you good luck
去年我就想來 但時間跟電腦營沖到...
I really wanted to come last year, but Computer Camp conflicted, and...
對她們好點 才能拍到好鏡頭
Act like you give a shit about them untiI they bring you into the good stuff
-看看  時機真對  -這次可棒透了
-Check it out. Perfect timing. -This is going to be classic
我的主要任務是保護 本校的學生...
My primary directive is to protect the students of this institution...
我看來像負責裸體枕頭大戰的人嗎?
Do I look like the guy that's in charge of the naked pillow fights, huh?
-隆二送一喔  -我左邊的大了點  看到沒?
-Two for the price of one. -My left one's bigger, see?
史提勒  我猜你是生來就要 擠袋子吹管子的
I think you were Just born to squeeze sacks and blow pipes, stifler
-今天要去市區嗎?  -今晚不去  我太累了
-Are you going into town? -Not tonight. I'm too tired
那些紫色的嘔吐物是意外 有人掉換了飲料桶
Dude, the purple puke was an accident. somebody switched the coolers
-小弟也加入家族企業了  -他是這麼說的嗎?
-little bro's Joining the family business. -ls that what he said?
來確保高三生都有個難忘懷的一天
Oh, we Just want to make sure the seniors have a very memorable last day
得讓大男孩透個氣 好啦  現在換我訂規則
Got to let the big boys breathe. AlI right, we play by my rules now
-機器人可以錄影嗎?  -好  你的企圖是啥?
-Can the robot record? -AlI right, so, what are your intentions?
-你知道你做了什麼嗎?  -不重要  他輸定了
-Do you know what you Just did? -Doesn't matter. He's going down
史提勒  怎麼你全家的 天份都到了史提夫身上?
Hey, stifler, how come steve got alI the talent in your family?
從明天起 將安排許多刺激的活動...
starting tomorrow, we have many, many exciting activities planned...
保持高橡園 公平和友善的競爭精神
to keep up that TalI Oaks spirit of fair play and friendly competition
喂  發情狗 在他們喝完前我們再去多拿點
Hey, horn dog, let's go get some more of these before they run out
把木頭弄暖些 再抹上一點油就行啦
get that wood nice and warm, slap on some valve oiI and go to town, yo
沒錯  而我們在這裡 兩個營區裡最酷的一夥...
True that. And here we are, the two dopest homeboys in camp...
秀點乳頭   長些睪丸 喂  大家保持暖身
show some tits. Grow some balls. Hey, keep that thing warm for me
-你確定行嗎?  -我生來就是色情明星耶
-Hey, you sure you can do this? -Hey, born to be a porn star, baby
丟出去時  讓球在指尖轉動 好嗎?
and when you throw it, let it rolI right off your fingers, alI right?
好  在你們看我的辛苦成果前 我有個條件
AlI right, one condition before I show you the fruits of my labors
別管他們  等他們看到錄影帶 就知道好歹了
screw them, dude. They're gonna freak out when they see the video
-他終於回你電話了?  -沒  但我有留話
-He finally called you back? -No, but I left him another message
我是山毛櫸高校的高三鼓手 布蘭頓凡德甘普...
I'm Brandon Vandecamp, senior drum maJor, Beechwood Academy...
-史提勒有弟弟?  -對  你在這裡幹嘛?
-There are two stiflers? -Yes, sir. Hey, what're you doing here?
-誰在你的短笛裡撒尿啦?  -我感覺你話裡有敵意
-Who pissed in your piccolo? -I'm sensing some hostility here
就是薩克斯風手忘記吹附點音符的? 噢  嗨
The one where the sousaphone player forgot to dot the l? Oh, hey
走廊對面的冰箱裡 是議員秘密貯藏啤酒的地方
The counselors have a secret stash in the fridge across the hall
別這麼古板好不好? 我可以幫你追那個美眉
PulI your panties out of your ass. I can help you with that chick
聽好喔  老兄 有一次在儀隊營  我還幹了雙簧管呢
Check it, dawg. This one time at Band Camp, I fucked an oboe
-如果我有辦法找到這個必卡多...  -你找到了?
-Wait, if I somehow found this Picard thing... -You found it?
-去死吧  豬臉  -老兄  你不行了喔
-Bite me, Fuck Face. -Come on, man, you're missing it
今晚有何節目? 要開派對  狂野一番吧?
so, what's going on tonight? We gonna party, get a little crazy?
另外我會在一周內 讓你把克洛依弄得爽歪歪
Plus, I'lI have you giving Chloe the pelvic noogie inside a week
麥特  行進很難的耶 這可不像丟橄欖球
Matt, marching's hard, okay? It's not like throwing some football
提醒大家  隨著冠軍獎盃的 競爭愈益激烈
Just a little reminder that as the battle for the cup heats up,
對  動快點  對  就這樣 轉圈  像這樣
Yeah, now faster. Yeah. Like that. A circle. Like that
好吧  既然我們這是 歐普拉真心話時間...
Okay, since we're having some big fucking Oprah moment here...
丹妮菈喜歡吉米 但她比他還高幾公分耶
Danielle likes Jimmy, but she's like a foot taller than him
大家都想在隱藏錄影帶上 看呆子做那些蠢事
People love to see dorks doing that freaky shit on hidden video
看來史提夫跟某人 辦完事就跑了
Well, it looks like steve gave someone the old stifler bang-and-boot
我那快4公斤重的成熟物 就吊在這裡呢  麗絲
Oh, I've got 10 pounds of dangling maturity right here, Leesy
我被困在那裡 讓竊窕奶媽檢查我的...
And I got stuck up there with Mrs. Doubtfire checking out my....
-嘿  奧斯卡  叫賣擴來  -拜託  閉嘴啦
-Hey, Oscar, somebody calI the Macro. -Dude, please, shut up
不  我是想既然來了 就該好好表現一下
No, look, I figure I'm here, I might as welI make the best of it
-嘿  硬屁股  怎麼樣?  -快來看看
-Hey, what's up, crust bucket? -Come here, dude. Check this out
-麥特  這是我的職責  -拿出老二   拍拍襪子
-Matt, that's my Job. -Grab your cocks and move your socks
-麥特  史提夫是電影製片天才  -真正的美國英雄
-steve is like a filmmaking genius. -A true American hero
我們只想說莎喲娜啦 讓你們這些蠢蛋知道...
We Just want to say sayonara, and let you fuck-necks know...
認命吧  高三生 別碰到胡椒噴霧喔
Payback, seniors. Don't get that pepper spray on your hands
麥特老兄  你不能跟儀隊女搞 別降低水準
Matt, buddy, you cannot screw band chicks. There are standards
-麥特史提勒跟他哥一樣是大混蛋  -衝突
-Matt stifler is pure eviI Just like his brother. -...conflict
你要走象步   做自慰圈 並喝大桶酒
with your elephant walks and circle Jerks and drinking butt beer
-你可否替我轉告他一件事?  -沒問題  小姐
-Could you send him a message for me? -No problem, senorita
你怎麼回事? 不敢露出被蚊子叮的小腫包嗎?
What's wrong with you? scared to show off the mosquito bites?
-是又怎樣?  -不  布蘭頓  他沒有
-Yeah, what if I am? -No, Brandon, that is not what he's doing
但只要在史提夫和他朋友旁邊 你就變成史提夫大師
but around steve and his friends, you were the stiffmeister
真不該用徹夜狂歡毀掉 一天的練習
Man, one night of fun was not worth losing a whole day of practice
-哇塞  看看你  -亞瑞娜  你在這幹嘛?
-Holy shit, look at you. -Arrianna, what are you doing here?
我跟布蘭頓搞過一次 還鼓手咧  他...
I hooked up with Brandon once. some drummer. He has...
-對  我的也是喔  -醫生能幫你整好
-Yeah, mine, too, baby. -They can totally fix that
好  準備啦  小兄弟 我會好好教你
AlI right, there we go, little buddy. I'm gonna fix you up good
-對  我得到我想要的  -你怎麼不閉上鳥嘴?
-Yeah, I get what I want. -Why don't you shut the fuck up?
奶油鹿肉   炸花枝和豬肉凍 放在同一個盤子裡
they had creamed venison, squid fritters, and Jellied pork
山毛櫸領先 大瀑布和羅伊暫居第二
Beechwood leads. Great Falls and Lloyd are tied for second
只要你把我的照片 從手機裡刪掉就行
As soon as you get rid of that picture of me on your phone
我認為他不該是你學習的榜樣
And I don't think those are the shoes you should be so eager to fill
新生要全程戴瓜帽 這是規定
Rookies are to wear their beanies at alI times. Those are the rules
拿的姿勢  像這樣 敲的姿勢  像這樣
Carrying position, like this, and playing position, like this
據我所知 伊麗絲  你為節目做了樂曲...
I understand you composed the music to your show, Elyse...
她會吹喇叭嗎? 因為她嘴上功夫真的很厲害
Did she play the trumpet? Because she has really strong lips
我需要知道史提夫大師 計畫裡的第二步是什麼
and I really need to know step Two in the stiffmeister plan
我喝得很醉 說不定會忘記...
I'm so drunk right now. I'm probably going to forget about you...
我們要跟樂團一起排練 你在這幹嘛?
We practice our routine with the band. What are you doing here?
天才新導演麥修史提勒製作...
in association with its talented new director, Matthew stifler...
我們明天還有比賽 我不想再見到你
so we got a contest to win tomorrow. And I don't want to see you
我看過各種想入學的辦法...
I've certainly seen some interesting attempts to gain admission...
-再見啦  吃屁鬼  -他比他哥還混帳
-Adios, butt-hugger. -He's a bigger asshole than his brother
《儀隊也瘋狂》 史提夫有對手了...
Bandeez Gone wild. steve's gonna have some competition now...
才不是  我們只是提醒他要戴瓜帽
That's not true, sir. We simply reminded him to wear his beanie
想不想說說你到底來幹嘛的? 史提勒?
You want to telI me what the helI you're doing here, stifler?
被聘來當今夏的麥擴 結果卻懷了孕
she was hired to be the Macro this summer, but she got pregnant
才不要  吉米才不要 把嘴巴放到那東西上
Hell, no. Jimmy ain't putting his lips on that thing
-我只是想幫他拿出來而已  -閉嘴啦
-I was Just trying to help him get it off, yo. -Dude, shut up
或許你該跟你朋友麥特多多相處
Maybe you should hang out with your friend Matt a little bit more
你可知道  史提夫以為 可稱作他朋友的那些人...
You know, the people steve thought were his friends...
怎麼? 想讓山毛櫸贏過我們?
AlI right, now. what, you want to let Beechwood tittie-fuck us?
各位  乾杯 明天起我們就高三啦
Gentle-fucks, a toast. Tomorrow, we begin our reign as seniors
這場表演代表我們的高三生涯...
This performance sets the tone for our senior year. I mean....
噢  吉姆搬了出去 娶了米雪...
Oh, well, Jim is now out of the house, married to Michelle...
規則很簡單 選一個類別和問題...
the rules are simple. You choose a category and a question...
麥特  你認為 伊麗絲是暴躁怪異的古板女...
And Matt, you think Elyse is an uptight, geeky prude...
-各位  開始練習  出發  -隨你便
-Okay, people, back to work, let's go. -Whatever
我今天把藍姆酒寄給你了 在呆瓜城那可能很有用喔
I sent you rum today. Could come in handy in Dorksville
別忘了擦防曬油 你的身體就是樂器喔
don't forget your sunscreen. Your bodies are your instruments
東大瀑布高中  可以入場了
East Great Falls, you may enter the field for competition
萊文史丹先生報告說 營區裡發生了幾件...
Mr. Levenstein reports that there were a few incidents...
喂  你只要記住 大家都支持你
Look, you Just remember that everybody here is pulling for you
你不學著體恤別人 就得被開除
Either you learn to be more considerate or you wilI be expelled
-請你代勞好嗎?  -這才像他媽的派對嘛
-Would you mind? -Now we're talking about a fucking party
目前卻只做到了鼻竇消毒而已 所以...
And, so far, you've only had your sinuses sanitized. so...
我在春假的一周內就釣上 三個啦啦隊員
I nailed three cheerleaders in one week on spring break.
-我們明天還要練習呢  -放鬆點  麗絲
-We have a big practice tomorrow, you guys. -Relax, Leesy
幫我擦背好嗎? 今天多曬了點太陽
Can you get my back? I think I got a little bit of sun today?
對  所以他才會到哪都帶著那根鼓棒
Yeah, that's why he carries that big stick around everywhere
-他們很不錯  -對  他們今年特別出色
-They're tight. -Yeah, they're better than ever this year
-我要他們活潑點  -你在這幹嘛  史提勒?
-I like them feisty. -What're you doing here, stifler?
今年  羅勃茲的校長蘇珊崔博士...
-This year, Dr. susan Choi, president of Robards...
我知道這有點呆 但這裡有傳統...
Oh, I know. It's a little silly, but it's tradition here...
歡迎來到史提勒之家 我是你的招待人  麥特
Hi, welcome to Casa de stifler. I'lI be your host, Matt
我都會誠摯地以 不需要踢你屁股作為目標
I'lI make it my sincere goaI not to have to kick your ass
各位  這是順利的第一天 我是麥擴...
Great first day, campers. This is your Macro speaking...
如果你不教我行進 我就再哭給你看
Well, if you don't teach me to march, I might Just cry again
我假裝氣喘病發 把兩個相機都換掉了
I faked an asthma attack, and I changed both of the cameras
你的小儀隊或許暫時領先...
Your little band may be leading in the competition, stifler...
我一直偷偷在拍 他們做這些蠢事
I've been secretly videotaping them doing alI this crazy shit
不管是誰的飲料桶 他都不該把催吐劑倒進去
He shouldn't have been dumping lpecac in anyone's cooler
怎麼? 你在儀隊營羞辱我還不夠?
What? lt wasn't enough for you to humiliate me at Band Camp?
我絕對能維持史提夫大師製片水準
that I'm up to the standards of the stiffmeister Productions
你是混帳嗎? 你全身是毛  臭得像屎
Are you an asshole? You're hairy, and you smelI like shit
-她們陷害我  -他用胡椒噴霧攻擊我們...
-They set me up. -He attacked us with pepper spray...
-你在幹嘛?  -等行進開始啊  女士
-What are you doing? -Awaiting my marching lesson, ma'am
有  被員警追過克利諾小溪時
Yes, ma'am, the time the cops chased us across Koreno's Creek
-他會搞砸的  -他一定會搞砸的
-He's gonna screw it up. -He's definitely gonna screw it up
-那又怎樣?  -那個大胖可以跟人搞?
-What's up with that? -That cock spring is getting laid?
但贏得羅伯茲獎學金卻像是...
But winning the Robards scholarship, I mean, that is like...
是全新配方的精子乳 百分之百的史提非精液...
It's a cum-pletely new formula. 100% stiffy Juice...
-我不跟儀隊人混  -我不是儀隊人
-I don't socialize with bandees. -I'm not a fucking bandee
但今年卻不一樣 今年  我們可以戰勝他們
But this year is different. This year, we can beat them
別忘了歡迎高橡園營區議員們
And let's not forget to welcome the TalI Oaks Camp Counselors
對了  身為正式儀隊怪胎成員...
Hey, you know, since I'm an officiaI band geek and all...
你不知道成龍在這吧?
You didn't know Jackie Chan was in the house, did you boys, huh?
他在我的湖畔小屋 把那紅發浪蕩女搞上床
He screwed that redheaded nympho chick at my lake house
但在這裡  你得戴頂小呆瓜帽...
But here, you Just have to wear a silly little hat and...
快上床去大睡一覺吧 因為...
so hop in the sack, and get a good night's sleep because...
尼爾森先生 這樣要扣大瀑布高中兩分吧
I believe that's two points from Great Falls, Mr. Nelson
-對  寶貝  我為你驕傲  -謝謝喔  翹臀珍
-Yeah, baby, you did me proud, son. -Thanks, J. Lo
就用必卡多來讓自己鎮靜下來
and I calm myself down by going off and playing on my Picardo
肩膀朝著目標  對 好  現在往前踏一步
shoulder to your target. Right. Okay, now step forward
這樣才能用隱藏相機拍到他們的鏡頭
I've been playing them so I could get them on hidden video
我們得第一! 我們得第一! 我們得第一!
We're Number One! We're Number One! We're Number One!
有名的羅伯茲音樂學校全年獎學金
a fulI scholarship to the prestigious Robards Conservatory
-這是儀隊營耶  呆子  -嘿  公平點...
-Well, it is Band Camp, moron. -Hey, to be fair...
整天把性掛在嘴上 只想媲美他那討人厭的哥哥
Just to gain the approvaI of his sociopathic brother
是卡布洛維茲遙控機器人 你完蛋啦
The Kaplowitz Remote Robotic Rover. And you are so busted
大家好  今天儀隊營的天氣真好啊
Hello, everyone. lsn't it a peachy day here at Band Camp?
你沒有第二步的睪丸和第三步的舌功
You don't have the balls for Two or the tongue for Three
這種事絕不會發生在老麥擴身上
These kinds of things would never happen with our old Macro
我回來後  馬上就輕了 一百萬個史提勒的重量
When I get back, I'lI be a million stiflers lighter
你為了報復 居然把我所有內衣都偷走...
You made it up to him by stealing alI my underwear...
-是你先的  -這可以讓我得到獎學金
-You started it. -This is gonna get me that scholarship
來吧  不准照相 你是乳仔隊嗎?
Hey, come on, no pictures. What're you, the papa-tit-zzy?
學校裡不准有人知道 三角鐵或瓜帽的事
Nobody at schooI hears about the triangle or the beanie
學校開課後  你最好規矩點
When schooI starts, you're going to be on a very short leash
你住在郊區 你不可能當混混的
You live in the suburbs. You ain't never gonna be a gangsta
帶睡袋來  方便萬一要開帳篷
Bring your sleeping bag, in case we decide to pitch a tent
我聽說  有人進了他辦公室...
I heard this one time, this kid went into that office...
你得開始放尊重點  史提勒
You need to start showing some respect around here, stifler
-什麼? 克洛依  他很討厭耶  -性感的討厭
-What? Chloe, he is so obnoxious. -sexy obnoxious
高橡園杯的比賽氣氛高漲
Competition for the TalI Oaks Cup is really heating up
每次我丟球  你就要跑去接嗎?
so every time I throw it, you're gonna run and go get it?
未經過濾的驚異大片 《儀隊也瘋狂》
unfiltered, and un-fucking-believable Bandeez Gone wild
崔博士  山毛櫸高校的 布蘭頓凡德甘普...
Now, Dr. Choi, Brandon Vandecamp from Beechwood...
各位先生女士 請起立歡迎畢業生
Ladies and gentlemen, please rise to honor our graduates
-謝謝  -我厭倦了混在那些...
-Thank you. -I'm tired of messing around with these...
誰不想看看裸體辣妹啊?
I mean, who doesn't like to look at hot naked chicks, right?
是我的  蠢鬼 還給我好不好?
It's mine, Jerk-wad. Now wilI you give it back?
總之  今晚有個營火思樂冰晚會...
Anyway, there's this bonfire-slushee party tonight...
好好跟朋友們 享受儀隊營的樂果吧
suckle the tender fruits of Band Camp with your friends
這是最後一個禮拜 該認真準備比賽了
we're in our finaI week. Time to put on our game faces
今天他們的音樂是由 資深鼓手...
Their music today was composed by senior drum major...
我們在想如果能來場特別首映...
Look, we thought that if we had an advance screening...
對  是畢業典禮 可不是波士頓交響樂團
Yeah, but it's graduation. lt ain't the Boston Pops
四年級起我就夠成熟了  麥特 你呢?
I've matured since the fourth grade, Matt. Have you?
我喊"儀隊十" 你就得立刻肅立
When I yelI "band 10 hut," you snap firmly at attention
數到一和三時踏左腳 二和四踏右腳
Left foot on one and three, right foot on two and four
我知道他很討厭 但他也有好處
I know he's a dick and everything, but he's also got one
他父親蘭敦也是 我們最大的捐助人
and his father, Landon, is our best donor, also by far
自從八年級後 你就沒跟我說過一句話
You haven't said a word to me since the eighth grade
對  因為你每次都這麼凶巴巴的
Yeah, and that tone of voice is exactly the reason why
拜託啦  老兄  我可以幫忙 我是史提夫大師耶
Come on, man. I can help. I'm the stiffmeister
-看  這有防霧鏡頭  笨  -對  好
-see, it's got an anti-fog lens. Duh. -Yeah, good
麥特  我真的沒時間跟你浪費
Look, Matt, I really don't have time for this right now
-謝謝  怪怪機器人  -不客氣...
-Thanks, little creepy machine. -You're welcome...
-我好像咬到舌頭了  -噢  我看看
-I think I bit a hole in my tongue. -Oh, let me see
而且他會贏 因為他會演奏樂器
which, you know, he wilI because he plays an instrument
唉呀! 看來雌性體選中了特別的伴侶
Crikey! The alpha female has chosen an unlikely mate
-我是胡扯的耶!  -卡住了
-I was Just fucking with you, dawg! -You.... It's stuck
導致年輕人把自己的樂器...
that we live in that causes young men to stick their...
布蘭頓  你是個好鼓手  所以...
Brandon, I think you're a really good drummer, so...
她是該年的前高橡園議員...
And, being a former TalI Oaks Counselor of the Year...
只准問橄欖球問題 準備脫衣吧  小姐們
FootbalI questions only. Prepare to strip, ladies
對了  我想知道晚上有啥節目
Look, I want to know what goes on at night, alI right?
我用它贏過去年的州際科展
But I did use it to win the state science Fair last year
我不曉得這是什麼意思 但一定有道理
I don't know what it means, but it's got to be good
你不擇手段 只想成為矚目焦點
You do whatever it takes to be the center of attention
-你說我們會贏嗎?  -當然啦
-You think we'lI win this thing? -Hell, yeah, we will
-儀隊十  一   二   準備  -糟了
-Band 10 hut. One, two, ready. -shit
那大家都會知道 你真的不是蠢蛋
then everyone would see that you're not really a dork
我看過幾百遍了 你他媽的屁屎人
I've seen it a million times, you fucking ass-booger
不過這是我第一次上臺...
I Just.... You know, it's my first time up here, and...
-快噴一下  -幹  才不要  誰找到就是誰的
-spray that shit. -Fuck, no. Finders keepers
大家努力練習吧 祝最棒的儀隊獲勝
Okay, so let's work hard, and may the best band win
你得把自己帶回你桌上 大胖狗
You need to show yourself back to your table, Big Dog
其中還有高橡園杯賽跑呢
not the least of which is the race for the TalI Oaks Cup
你坐中間 你的遊戲  我來分配座位
You sit in the middle. Your game, my seating chart
-等等  有人想喝啤酒嗎?  -我要
-wait. But first, does anybody want a beer? -I do
對  但比低音鼓接力好多了
Yeah, but it's better than the bass drum relay
伊麗絲  放輕鬆點 好好享受
Come on, Elyse. Cut loose a little bit. Have some fun
希望那個機器人和飲料沒嚇到你
I hope I didn't scare you with the Rover and the soda
他居然跟蘋果派搞過呢
who actually engaged in sexuaI congress with an apple pie
我們要贏得比賽 就得好好努力
we want to win this thing, we've gotta bust our asses
去他的挑戰 我要去踢他屁股
Man, screw that challenge. I'm Just gonna kick his ass
-有人知道這事嗎?  -他們知道
-Does anybody know about this yet? -Oh, they do now
-好啦  刪掉了  -現在可以看錄影帶了吧?
-There. Done deal. -Now can we see the video?
不  凡德甘普先生 因剽竊被取消資格
No, Mr. Vandecamp was disqualified for plagiarism
來自未來  引導年輕幼稚的心靈
sent back in time to guide young and innocent minds
-你用這個看過美眉裙下嗎?  -沒
-You ever use this to look up chicks' skirts? -No
很有趣對不對? 對極啦
That's funny for you dorks. Yeah, it is, isn't it? Yeah
這聽來像你不正常的榮譽心作祟
This sounds like your overactive honor-society brain
-你就得丟橄欖球  對吧?  -好
-you have to throw the football, alI right? -Okay
我不要任何人以為我是儀隊豬頭
I don't want anybody to think I'm a dorky-ass bandee
史提勒  我說過不想再看到你了
I told you I don't want to see you anymore, stifler
我等這一刻已經等很久了
I've been waiting for this moment for a very long time
你想怎樣  開除我嗎? 雪曼終結者?
What're you going to do, expeI me, shermanator?
他說在儀隊營 整天都可在床上搞
And he said alI they do at Band Camp is screw 24l7
然後他惡意地對布蘭頓的私處施暴
And then he viciously assaulted Brandon's genitals
無疑肇因於你所隱射的事實
No doubt due to the tendencies you alluded to earlier
-有麻煩嗎?  -不  一切都很好
-ls there a problem here? -No, everything's fine
哈羅  小姐們 伊麗絲  真高興又見到你
Hola, chicas. Elyse, so good to see you again
《儀隊也瘋狂》 第一幕 派對真男人
Bandeez Gone wild. scene One. Party hombre
身上都是刺青的那個 那個大喇叭手
Dude, the one with alI the tattoos. The Tubanator
這些凡夫俗子把你當英雄了
You know, these plebes think you're some kind of hero
-你知道?  -你總是這樣  騙人
-You do? -It's what you always do. You're a fake
-多用點臀部  -像這樣嗎?
-Use your hips more. -Hips, like that?
真夠呆 我要用電子郵件寄給大家看
What a dork. I'm going to emaiI this to everybody
-怎麼樣? 好玩嗎?  -還好
-so how's it going? Are you having fun? -It's okay
-謝謝你們  -謝他吧  是他的點子
-Thank you so much. -Thank him. lt was his idea
真嚇人  這是史迪力丹樂團呢
Bite my nuts and calI me skippy. It's a steely Dan
不重要  大胖 他待不久的
lt don't matter, Big O. He ain't gonna be here long
你是史提夫史提勒的弟弟吧?
You're steve stifler's younger brother, aren't you?
各種瘋狂的事 裸體枕頭大戰等等
AlI the crazy shit. Naked pillow fights, whatever
沒穿高橡園制服T恤 也沒戴瓜帽
No standard-issue TalI Oaks T-shirt and no beanie
逮到我正在拍大學美眉洗澡鏡頭
busted me taping some college chicks in the shower
我終於能聽見音樂的召喚了喔
Hey, I can finally hear the music calling me, okay?
我確定這大概只是...
Well, I'm pretty sure it's probably Just something...
-我只想尊重你  -噢  你真好
-I just want to be respectful. -Oh, that's sweet
離別是甜蜜的悲傷 尤其當你慘敗
Parting is such sweet sorrow. When you're a loser
-就是樂團的演奏啊  -好運?
-You know, on the whole music thing. -Good luck?
有個完美的懲罰 非常適合你的罪行
I know the perfect punishment to fit your crime
我不是說跟她們搞 呆頭鵝
I'm not talking about screwing them, scrotum-breath
因為他的弟弟我將加入家族企業啦
because little bro's Joining the family business
誰想累積一些貴寶上床里程啊?
Who wants to rack up a few frequent fucker miles?
用想跟處女上床的方法 去解決吧
Think of it like trying to hook up with a virgin
你就舉高你的樂器 然後...
you're gonna move your instrument out, and then...
讓我知道你何時想學新動作
You let me know if you want to learn some new moves
史提勒  昨天你表演得不錯嘛
Quite a little show you put on yesterday, stifler
-這真是好喝  -別喝太多了
-This is some good shit. -Don't enJoy it too much
抱歉  這種動作我做得很差
I'm sorry. I'm really no good at this stuff
這輩子沒人對我這麼好過
Nobody's ever been that sweet to me in my whole life
超級有名  有時候我真...
like holy-shit famous. And, sometimes, I Just....
對不起  我不知道怎會這樣
You know, I'm so sorry. I don't know what happened
對  沒人能比他好
Yeah, there's Just no way you could ever be this good
五次衛冕高橡園杯冠軍...
And five-time defending TalI Oaks Cup Champion...
你知道我最喜歡哪首音樂嗎?
can you guess what my favorite piece of music is?
-穿這件蠻時髦的高橡園T恤  -是哦
-a somewhat stylish TalI Oaks T-shirt. -Yeah
聽來像是我愛玩的 要開始了嗎?
This looks like my kind of game. shalI we play?
隨便啦  他自己脫掉褲子的...
Oh, whatever. He took his own pants off....
說到瓜帽  史提勒你的呢?
Yes, speaking of beanies, where's yours, stifler?
-我以前...  -鏡頭起霧  不!
-I used to be.... -Lens fog. No!
-什麼事?  -你的鼓打得很棒
-What's up? -Your drum line sounds pretty tight
我不太談這些...
I mean, I don't really talk about it alI that much...
對  你可不想在獨奏時破裂
Yeah, you don't want to be chapped for your solos
停止當個舔屁鬼
why don't you quit being such a fucking taint licker,
他會回電的  才三禮拜而已
He'lI get back to me. It's only been three weeks
只有畢業生可參加 但你可過來
and it's only for the grads, but you could come
那兩顆怎麼樣? 還是又小又翹嘛
How they hanging? stilI smalI and perky, I see
娶了那個儀隊浪女米雪
he married this freaking nympho band-geek, Michelle
-祝你在儀隊營愉快  -謝謝  我會的
-Have fun at Band Camp. -Thank you, I will
-百分百的真男人  -好  今晚八點來我房間
-100% hombre. -AlI right, my room, 8:00
對了  今天的士氣真高昂啊
and, hey, morale couldn't have been higher today
-不要這樣叫我  -好啦  快點
-Quit calling me that. -Okay, okay, moving on
那個大男孩會喜歡慢慢走回去的
Yeah, the big boys wilI love the long walk home
你終於出櫃啦 恭喜你
so you finally came out of the closet. Good for you
-看著吧  -他又要闖禍了
-Let's see. -Look. He's getting in trouble again
-我花粉熱過敏呀  -那時是冬天  小麥特
-I had allergies. -lt was winter, Mattie
跟需不需要無關 是想不想要
It's not a matter of need. It's a matter of want
不  呆子 你們都上臺演奏
No, you idiot. You each get on stage and perform
-我很愉快啊  一直都很愉快  -對
-I have fun. I have fun alI the time. -Yeah
因為這獎盃是屬於團隊的...
because the cup is, like, a team thing, and....
大家聽好  你們這些懶蟲
AlI right, listen up, you lazy bunch of lip shits
在我忘掉前  得快去把它寫下來
I've got to go write this down before I forget
拿包包  待會見了  儀隊兄
Get the bags. Guess I'lI see you around, bandee
雪麗跟那個鼓手大胖上床了
sheree slept with that big Oscar guy, the drummer
-伊麗絲  你該放鬆點  -我很好啊
-Elyse, you need to relax, girl. -I'm fine
某位高橡園的高三作曲家可榮獲...
one senior TalI Oaks composer is awarded...
而我跟年輕人交往密切...
And I have a great rapport with young people...
-怎麼會呢?  -她們騙我脫光...
-May I ask why? -Well, they got me naked...
就算胡椒噴霧的代價吧 混蛋
this wilI make up for the pepper spray, asshole
-放鬆點  老友  -別那麼硬
-Try and relax, dawg. -Not so hard
我要雙簧單簧管   黑東西...
I want the oboe, clarinet, black thingies...
還要全面的節奏小隊
and we've got the rhythm section in a full-on blitz
噢  天哪  我再也不會犯那種錯了
Oh, God, I'lI never make that mistake again
各位  太棒了  鼓手  數到五
Girls, that was great. Percussion, take five
-你遲到了  -對啦  快開窗
-You're late. -Yeah, no shit. Open the window
一小時後到會場集合
Direct yourselves to the marching field in one hour
-你也是  小鬼  -等一下
-You, too, little man. -Wait, wait, wait, wait
克洛伊  我們沒看到伊麗絲裸體 真的
Chloe, we never saw Elyse, you know, naked
喂  我們應該噴畢業證書才對
Dude, we should've sprayed the diplomas
既然你對儀隊很感冒...
since you have so much trouble with the band...
女士們  儀隊營的明天會更好
Band Camp Just got a whole lot better, ladies
你已經害我們損失五分了
You already cost us five points in the standings
我去維修部拿稀膠劑
I'lI get the paint thinner from maintenance
希望明年秋天能進入麻省理工學院
And I'm hoping it gets me into MlT next fall
已有三年沒人跟我挑戰了
It's been three years since I've been challenged
嘿  各位  雪麗要教我新動作
Hey, guys, sheree's gonna show me some moves
不管吃下什麼 都會很快吐出來
Whatever's in there should be out soon enough
他是否能撐過這場危險的遭遇...
WilI he survive this dangerous encounter...
我要你把手機上的照片刪掉
I want that picture on that camera phone erased
我們很努力  我們也夠格...
We've worked hard, and we are good enough...
這個家族企業 小弟不幹了
Guess little bro's quitting the family business
大家可別再奏錯曲子
I don't want anyone starting the wrong song again
-豎笛從屁眼插了進去  -什麼?
-Clarinet up the ass backwards, yo. -What?
讓我帶你去看你的新房間
Allow me to show you to your new accommodations
哦  你在雙掩護下進過球嗎?
Oh, you ever thrown into double coverage?
我以前很緊張  你知道...
I Just get stressed out, you know. I mean...
但口渴時別忘了告訴我們
but make sure to let us know if you get thirsty
我不是啦 我只是裝的
I'm not. Look. I've Just been acting like a geek
史提夫  你就像你哥
You know, you're like your brother, steve
-這是你安排的?  -還有朋友幫忙
-You planned alI this? -With some friends
這遊戲不是都跟音樂有關吧?
You didn't telI me this shit was about music
-沒有啦  -今天的節目...
-No, no hole. -On today's...
要把他媽的山毛櫸 沖出鎮外
Gonna ride fucking Beechwood out of the town
唯一會搞的人在這裡
The only person who's gonna get laid around here
我會把啦啦隊球放到窗戶做記號
I'lI leave my pompoms in the window for you
但我可以幫某人得到她應得的
But I can help someone get what she deserves
-這不是崔博士的簽名  -什麼?
-This is not Dr. Choi's signature. -What?
酷  今晚要露宿...
That's cool. so, there's a campout tonight...
明天如何? 實在太棒了
How about tomorrow? This is going to be great
奧斯卡   吉米  帶這人去...
Oscar, Jimmy, escort this man to see...
他贏了  山毛櫸會得五分...
Beechwood gets five points if he wins...
高橡園的盛大比賽開始!
Let the TalI Oaks Battle Royale begin
-沒用  -這是我的營區  混蛋
-Dildos. -This is stilI my camp, asshole
這是才藝表演的固定項目 裸體
It's their talent show routine, au naturel
你這個奸詐的網路怪客  太酷了
Dude, you filthy little cyberfucker. shit
對  只不過我可不舔自己的老二
Yeah, except I don't lick my own balls.
記住  雪曼終結者 什麼都看得清清楚楚
Remember, the shermanator sees it all
因為史提夫大師掌控一切
now that the stiffmeister's running the show
開始進行畢業幹典禮行動
Time to initiate Operation Gradu-fuck-uation
-麥擴到底是他媽的什麼東西?  -麥擴
-What the fuck's a macro? -The Macro
就是你說的紅發浪蕩女
that redheaded nympho chick that you spoke of
今晚跟真正的男人一起狂歡吧
Let's party with a reaI hombre tonight.
解決你們差異的唯一辦法...
the only way to solve your differences...
下午一點有鐵鈸課
I think there's a cymbaI class at 1:00
是我見過最討厭的樂器
That's the most annoying one I could think of
我不知道你是指誰  凡德怪人
I don't know what a plebe is, Vande-creep
我以為我們要一起看
Hey, I thought we were Just going to watch.
都被他媽的果汁酒弄得醉醺醺
AlI tripped out on the fucking fruit punch
你來吹  我來拉
Maybe you should blow on it and I'lI pull
或許是過度刺激的年代...
so maybe it's the over-stimulated times...
那些山毛櫸爛人可沒有休息
Those Beechwood plebes aren't taking breaks
如果要我敲三角鐵...
Hey, if I have to ring the triangle...
毫無節奏  根本無法持久
no rhythm, and he can't even bang very long
東大瀑布目前領先...
with East Great Falls in the lead...
山毛櫸必須贏得錦標賽才行
Beechwood has to win the Band Camp Playoffs
機會來了 讓我們贏得獎盃!
and this is our time, so let's win the cup
史提夫看過我的導演功力後...
After steve sees my directing talent...
我是精密的諮詢機器...
I am a sophisticated counseling machine...
我去把這東西替你放好
I'lI Just go and put this stuff away for you
別洩漏出去  我就給你看
Keep it between us, and I'lI let you watch
你爸請了誰替你作曲呢?
And who'd your daddy hire to compose yours?
機器人博士要準備上床啦
The time has come for Dr. Robot to get laid
你又為我翹起來啦  奧斯卡?
Are you standing up for me again, Oscar?
應該在幾分鐘內會消腫
The swelling should go down in a few minutes
我長大時還沒有MTV音樂頻道
We didn't have MTV when I was growing up
準備披掛上陣
And time to strap yourselves in for a bumpy ride
-不  那是尾巴  -隨便你啦
-No, that's its tail. -Whatever you say
-哇塞  這真可笑  -微笑
-Holy shit, this is so hilarious. -smile
各位  明天就是決賽了
The finaI performance is tomorrow, you guys
因為你偷拍我們...
'Cause the shit you got us doing on tape....
-根本不喜歡他  -什麼?
-really didn't like him very much. -What?
現在奧斯卡在樹林裡
I mean, right now, Oscar's off in the woods
-你要去儀隊營  -儀隊營!
-You're going to Band Camp. -Band Camp!
很快就會認識新朋友了
and you'lI be making new friends in no time
-我先   "誰吹我? "  -好
-I'lI go first. "Who Blew Me?" -Good
你想用錄影機做什麼?
With the video, I mean. What are you doing?
現在我得對他諂媚點
so now I have to be alI nice to him and shit
-你要怎樣?  -踢扁你
-What are you going to do? -Kick your ass
怎麼樣? 我要享受去了
You know what? I am going to have some fun
有小號   喇叭   節奏和笛子
Got horns, trumpets Rhythm and flutes
-糟糕  要我幫忙?  -別碰我
-shit, you want help? -Don't touch me
你不懂  她簡直...
you don't understand. she's like famous...
你以前做的比這個好
What you had before was way better than this
-好  -準備好了? 很好
-Okay. -You're fine. Ready? There you go
當然好  明天黃昏時這裡再見
Yeah, sure. I'lI see you here at sunset
-開玩笑的吧?  -太棒了
-You're kidding me, right? -That's great
沒人會知道有這卷錄影
No one's gonna know about your little video
五次衛冕冠軍...
Your five-time defending champion...
嗨  史提勒  你拿什麼來現?
Hey, stifler, where's your instrument?
我會向史提夫證明...
Hey, look, I'm going to prove to steve...
這是史提夫大師送的畢業禮物
A graduation gift from the stiffmeister
-聖瑪莉山高中  -聖瑪莉山高中!
-Mount st. Marie. -Mount st. Marie!
來過儀隊營的男人中最性感的
Most sexy man ever to come to Band Camp
把冷氣關掉就行了
Just gotta turn down the A.C. in there, huh?
-把他的衣服藏起來  -丟到窗外去
-Ditch his clothes. -Out the window
踏進對方領域一步呢?
by putting one foot in front of the other?
那什麼東西? 跟蹤氣嗎?
What is that thing, butt weasel?
我也知道為什麼你的相機會壞
And I know why your camera spritzed out
-你真的是蘇格蘭人?  -當然不是
-Are you really scottish? -Fuck, no
-對  聽來真噁心  -才不呢
-Yeah, that sounds gay. -It's not gay
搞什麼屁啊? 我真是不懂
Fucking hoes, man. I don't get that shit
我們明年要畢業了 我不知道
we graduate next year, and I don't know
好  但我需要點時間暖身
Okay, but it takes me a while to warm up
對  史提夫跟他朋友都到場了
Yeah, steve showed up with his friends
這樣就要我們原諒他?
so we're Just supposed to forgive him now?
一定是你們弄錯了  看...
No, there must be some mistake. see...
或許你該跟他們做朋友
perhaps you should make friends with them
好耶  河谷辣妹也瘋狂
AlI right, steve! Valley Girls Gone wild
誰選你當怪胎鎮市長的?
And who made you the mayor of Geek Town?
"猛撞寶貝"和 "誰吹我? "
"Banging Babes," and "Who Blew Me?"
或許我們該讓他一步
maybe we should Just give him a head start
-愛情和浪漫大師  -吹牛
-Master of love and romance. -Bullshit
你認識幾個奧斯卡啊? 快去
How many other Oscars do you know? Go!
沒錯  我們可能想再看一次
Exactly, we may want to watch it again
正好可以教你新動作
Now's a good time to teach you those moves
他對活栓油過敏
He had an allergic reaction to the valve oil
-什麼?  -錄影帶被我刪掉了
-What? -The video, man, I deleted it
曾偷拍你們的事  我無法收回...
I can't take back spying on you...
天哪  各位  真是太棒了
Oh, my God, you guys, that was amazing
-什麼?  -這是雙頭震動棒
-A what? -It's a double-headed dildo
不受另一位史提勒的摧殘
from the menace that is another stifler
你最棒的一面我們還沒看呢
and we haven't seen your best side yet
重整隊形  前排過來
Reset the block. Front ranks, right here
奧斯卡  你幫我拿飲料啦?
Oscar, brought me something to drink?
你在快速行進下踢過正步嗎?
You ever high-stepped in double time?
催吐劑萃取自天然藥草...
lpecac is a naturaI herbaI extract...
來吧寶貝 再多跳些舞?
Come on baby Do you do more than dance?
好  各位  休息一下
Okay, people, let's take a break
我們不是在行進耶  一腳就好
Come on we're not marching. One foot
喇叭手  我們要加強音調
Horns, we've got to work on intonation
好啦  現在可開始了嗎?
Fine. Like, now can we get on with it?
何況這裡的人棒多了
Besides, they're much hotter here
-他還是一樣混蛋  -沒錯
-He's stilI an asshole. -You're right
你有時候真是個混蛋...
You really are an asshole sometimes...
現在終於到了省悟的一刻
And now, the day of reckoning has come
也是高橡園議長
and the president of the TalI Oaks Council
-你得戴瓜帽  -是喔
-You wilI have to wear a beanie. -Yeah
嗨  爾尼卡布洛維茲  高音薩克斯風
Hey, Ernie Kaplowitz, tenor sax
這是1978年俄亥俄州表演...
This is a 1978 Ohio state show...
-四而長  -當然  沒問題
-Fourth and Long. -sure, no problem
對我們有些人來說 這是最後機會
For some of us, it's our last shot
-雙腳距離平均  -什麼?
-Keep your step size even. -My what?
我是陌生人 來看就知道
well, I'm hot blooded Check it and see
-真的?  -先吹一下...
-Really? -Blow in it for a while...
喝  我們在高橡園 喝果汁
Yo, we at TalI Oaks sipping on juice
-關燈啦  -該死  老兄
-Turn off the lights. -Damn, gangsta
一切都是為了儀隊   儀隊   儀隊
It's alI about band, band, band
但我得喝得很醉才行
But I'm going to have to be really drunk
等等  我有更好的點子...
No, wait. I've got a better idea...
那是多少  30的嗎? 很黏
What is that, 30? It's really thick
我們可否明天再來一次?
Could we do this again tomorrow night?
彩色夜視器? 我買了
Color night vision? I'lI take it. shit
進去是男中音 出來就變男高音了
a baritone and came out a soprano
哦  我知道你們的把戲了
AlI right, I see where this is going
你還是不守規則啊?
You stilI not following the rules, huh?
凡德抽筋  你覺得這樣如何?
How do you like that Vande-cramp?
我想該試試新辦法了
I think it's time to try a new approach
我幹嘛贏得他們的信任?
Why would I want to earn their trust?
麥特  天哪  對不起
Matt. Oh, my God. Matt, I am so sorry
真期待能提醒大家原因
I look forward to reminding people why
這次又怎麼回事? 克萊兒?
What happened this time, Claire?
嘿  你還沒聽到第五步耶
Hey, you haven't heard step Five yet
看  那個像白兔
Look, that one looks like a bunny
-什麼意思?  -八年級的朗誦課
-What? -The eighth grade recital
不  我不是 喂  告訴你...
No, I don't. Look, I told you...
-真的?  -對  我可以給你看
-Really? -Yeah, I could show you
對啊  今年的儀隊實在很棒
I know. It's a great crop this year
-我的天!  -真是不可思議
-Oh, my God. -That is unbelievable
來點催吐劑吧  凡德蟑螂?
How about some lpecac, Vande-cooch?
我看看有沒有空  好啊
Let me check my schedule. Hell, yeah
改變未來為時未晚
It's not too late to change your future
我說過史提夫會回我的
Told you steve'd get back to me
聽聽羅伊紀念高中!
Let's hear it from Lloyd MemoriaI High
士氣與衝突解決人員
Morale And Conflict Resolution Officer
應該要放輕鬆並被人搞一下
who needs to loosen up and get laid
現在可以表現了  呆子
Now you're representing, fool
口水量夠裝半打飲料了
We'lI have enough spit for a six-pack
那就是你那又酷又瘋狂的點子?
That was your cool, crazy idea?
不包括臉上這個
That doesn't include the ones on my face
對  因為我們多得是這個
Yeah, 'cause there's plenty of this
有一天你會感謝我的  混蛋
some day, you'lI thank me, asshole
我也無法贏回儀隊獎盃
and I can't win that Bandee Cup thing
讓你兄弟認識些酷音樂
Hook a brother up with some mad beats
跟那個女議員雪麗跳舞
tapping that counselor biatch, sheree
我在這裡時  你就在那裡
When I'm out here, you're in there
別怕  史提夫大師來了
Never fear, the stiffmeister's here
我們從未贏過山毛櫸高校
we've never beaten Beechwood, okay?
等等  什麼是航空總署?
Wait, there's a space Association?
贏者可得五分
The prize is five points towards the cup
-你完蛋了  -不  我才不
-You're going down. -No, I'm not
對啊  她還滿喜歡的哪
Yeah, I think she actually liked it
我說過  信任史提夫大師
I told you, trust the stiffmeister
是個便宜貨  但我弄丟了
It's Just a cheapie, but I lost it
東大瀑布領先四分
East Great Falls by four points
看? 我教了你些事情吧?
see? I taught you something. What?
如果你把風笛也加進去就會
lf you write in a bagpipe part.
我好幾天不敢出房間
I didn't come out of my room for days
隆重推出一刀未剪...
is happy to premier the unedited...
-該死  -柳橙汁難喝死了
-Damn. -That orange shit is Janky
小史提夫教養有小成
some progress made with stiffy Junior
史提夫的屎臉朋友吉姆...
steve's shit-head friend, Jim...
-我不知道  -"核桃鉗"
-I have no idea. -The Nutcracker
麥擴會給你好看  呆子
Macro gonna fuck your ass up, fool
我是麥擴  萊芬史丹先生
I'm the Macro, Mr. Levenstein.
噢  天  你不是史提勒吧?
Oh, my, you're not a stifler?
"四而長" "性音交融"
"Fourth and Long," "sextuplets,"
你們何不從明天起...
so why don't you start tomorrow...
能刺激反胃作用
that triggers the regurgitation reflex
我認識一個年輕人...
I knew a certain young man once...
我是說你很愉快
No, I was talking about you having fun
-大家都懂嗎?  -懂!
-Are you with me, bandees? -Yeah!
山毛櫸高校之能眾所皆知
It's no surprise Beechwood is good
你跟儀隊曾有短期的和睦相處
you bonded with the band briefly
-哇塞  -還有刻名字
-Holy shit. -It's even got a name
歡迎來到高橡園2005
welcome to TalI Oaks 2005
這次我原諒你的不禮貌
I'lI ignore that kind of talk once
所以我自願代勞了
so I Just stepped in and volunteered
每答錯一題就要脫一件
and every time you miss, you strip
-這種事誰會知道啊?  -抱歉啦
-Yeah, like I'd know. -sorry
好  誰要享受長頸啊?
AlI right, who wants a long neck?
-少來了  -真體帖喔
-Come on. -Good looking out, baby
扣大瀑布高中五分
Make it five points from Great Falls
我就當儀隊爛人間諜
I'lI be an undercover bandee fucker
當我喊:  "舉起" ...
Now when I call, "horns up"...
就知道  我們輸掉五分
Figures. We Just lost five points
那是德文的 "大師"之意
Meister means "master" in German
我說過該讓我掌舵的
I told you, you should let me steer
而不是你那下流   潮濕...
lnstead of your nasty, wet...
要不要我帶必卡多來?
should I bring that Picardo thing?
我非來不可  學校逼的
I had to come. The schooI made me
小姐  沒時間敦親睦鄰了
Ladies. No time for fraternizing
"雙D罩杯雪麗"短片段
A little "Double-D sheree" action
我就說吧
That's what I'm talking about, yo
我們計畫贏得州獎
we plan on winning the state title,
好  各位  休息一下
Okay, people, let's take a break
儀隊人來了  快溜
The bandees. Let's get out of here
敗壞好而純真的一切
defiling alI that is good and pure
你是新生嗎? 好像迷路了
Are you a rookie? You look lost
是那些拿儀仗的蠢蛋先動手的
Those knob-slobbers started it
-你死定了  -好了  各位
-You're dead. -Now, gentlemen
《Frankenstein》 恐怖片
Frankenstein. scary stuff
-他對我的儀隊下毒  -什麼?
-He poisoned my band. -What?
順其自然吧  麥特
so, Just go with the flow, Matt...
我看看我是否弄懂了
Let me see if I have this straight
天  這地方真是爛透了
Man, this place sucks donkey ass
對  是KR三號  寶貝
Yeah, it's the KR3, baby
儀隊夥伴  怎麼樣啊? 尤?
Band buds. How's it going? Yo
什麼東西? 是誰做的?
What the hell? Who's doing this?
-那是什麼?  -你的樂器
-What's that? -Your instrument
麥特  你對他單挑
Matt, you challenged him to a duel
但這不是他的錯...
But I know it's not his fault....
我正在練習獨奏...
Well, I was working on my solo...
準備上下其手吧
Prepare to Jam with the bearded clam
哇  你該用笛子試試
Hey, maybe you should try a flute
抽我屁股   叫我牛仔吧
smack my ass and calI me cowboy
-用臀部  -對  臀部
-Use your hips. -Oh, yeah, hips
大家今天都有點沒精神
we're alI a little sluggish today
你叫我把你寫進去
You made me write in a part for you
好掛在旗杆上
so you could run them up the flagpole
天哪  真的嗎?
Oh, my God. Are you serious?
柳橙汁真的很難喝啊
Hey, that orange shit is Janky, yo
那只是明信片...
I mean, it was Just a postcard...
各位都知道  每年...
Now, as you know, each year...
將親自評審樂曲
wilI judge the compositions herself
我就是史提夫的弟弟麥特
Yeah, I'm steve's brother, Matt
你會覺得有趣...
and you wilI have loads of fun...
這裡又沒有別人...
I mean, there's nobody around...
我真的很想到航空總署工作
I really want to work for NAsA
我的室友機器人博士...
Hey, my roommate, Dr. Robot...
聽到沒? 對  我也聽到了
There. Hear it? Yeah. Me, too
準備擁抱愛情吧
Get ready to cuddle the love puddle
崔博士會來  我是說...
Dr. Choi is coming. I mean...
我是說真的很醉很醉
I mean really drunk. Really drunk
來吧  混蛋們  繼續練
Come on, bitches. Back to work
這是戰備狀況  戰備!
we're at war here, people, war!
好了  高橡園...
AlI right, TalI Oakers...
很好吧? 又暖又鹹吧?
Good, huh? Warm and salty? Yeah
他們恥笑了我好久
They gave me so much shit for that
你敲三角鐵耶  真可愛
You play the triangle. How cute
是我們最棒的音樂家...
is our best musician by far...
我跟崔博士有約
I have an appointment with Dr. Choi
不  開除你太容易了
No, expulsion would be too easy
我是說偷偷錄影
I'm talking about videotaping them
伊麗絲  今年該你贏
Elyse, this is your year to win
你知道  你是...
You know, you are the most...
我接受  五點在露天音樂場
I accept. Amphitheatre, 5:00
你用鼓棒在戳我?
ls that your drumstick poking me?
或許你該吹一下
Maybe you should blow on it
吉米要當隊友
Jimmy should be a team player
對  現在沒空跳舞
Yeah, well, no time for dance.
吉米  你這個乳液鬼
Jimmy, you fucking lotion lover
-不會吧?  -一顆
-No way. -One ball
上面有他的另一顆睪丸呢
It's got his other balI on top
星際日期: 2005年8月21日
August 21, 2005
我不是要你們原諒我
I'm not asking you to forgive me
你還要把我騙來這裡?
Now you have to set me up here?
你爸開中國餐廳
Your dad owns a Chinese restaurant
說謊  你這鼻涕鬼
That's a lie, you dick-snot.
對了  凡德抽筋...
TelI you what, Vande-cramp...
-不!  -想看嗎?
-No!-want to see?
巴西蘭姆酒喝上癮羅
Locked into sweet Brazilian rum
是徒勞無功
episode wasting time on lost causes
好  布蘭頓  你先
Okay, Brandon, you're up first
東大瀑布得五分!
Okay, five points to Great Falls
我媽叫我學的
My mom made me learn an instrument
你今晚要變成誰呢?
Who're you going to be tonight?
把手臂後拉  對
Draw your arm back. There you go
說得沒錯
That's what I'm talking about
大家真的都討厭我哥嗎
Did everybody hate my brother?
他居然撇下我們投向儀隊!
He went fucking bandee on us
哇  快轉檯
Man, change the channel, yo
你叫做吉姆周赫平
Your name is James Hi Ping Chong
笨蛋   笨蛋   笨蛋  傻瓜
Dork. Dork. Dork. Goose
麥特  你在這幹嘛?
Matt, what're you doing here?
-可惡  -噢耶! 中獎!
-shit. -Oh, yeah! Jackpot!
需要行為矯正
Behavior modification is required
天  布蘭頓  沒事吧?
God, Brandon, are you okay?
別怕  沒關係的
Don't be scared. It's alI right
-你向我挑戰?  -不
-Are you challenging me? -No
麥特  這事很嚴肅耶
Matt, this is serious, okay?
現在給他好看
Now you show him, Brandon
看來比賽結束了
well, seems this contest is over
錯  這是第四步了
No, actually, it's step Four.
放到這麼怪異的地方
instruments in such odd places
所以這種事情...
so, you're perfectly normal...
味道怎樣? 凡德雞?
How's that taste, Vande-cock?
把球放到耳際...
Draw the balI over your ear...
-跑哪去了?  -那邊
-Where'd he go? -There he is
你穿錯制服羅
Dude, you're in the wrong uniform
-找到電話了  -說吧
-I got the number. -Go ahead
崔博士想要見我?
Dr. Choi wants to meet with me?
必卡多是短笛的牌子名
Picardo is a brand of piccolo
你哥一定很驕傲
Your brother must be very proud
我是伯裡斯卡洛夫迷
I am Just a Boris Karloff nut
老天  你是吉米的老爸
Holy shit, you're Jim's dad
脫鞋  再選一題
Lose the shoes, and pick again
抱歉  混蛋  玩完啦
sorry, asshole, game's over
請別搗亂了  好嗎?
Just stop screwing up, okay?
把瓜帽戴到他頭上
set the man up with his beanie
麥特  你來這裡...
Matt, you were sent here...
一   二   三  中間
One, two, three, middle.
贏家註定是...
And the winner by forfeit is...
等等  必卡多是你的?
Wait, you have.... Picardo?
我有得是時間
I have alI the time in the world
東大瀑布勝利
Victory, East Great Falls
就像跟小狗玩接球
Like playing fetch with my dog
或許像只有一個睪丸的白兔
Maybe a bunny with one nut
和全人類...
and all, indeed alI mankind...
我們這裡不說髒話的
We don't speak that way here
好酷! 我也是新生
Cool! I'm a rookie here, too
我把他的瓜帽...
what if I took his beanie...
站好  別亂動
stay still. stop moving
國家肛交協會?
NationaI AnaI sex Association?
你被嚇哭了
And you got so scared, you cried
讓群眾決定輸贏
And the crowd decides who wins
不能比倒立喝酒嗎?
Can't we Just do keg stands?
我的未來 你知道嗎?
my future, you know? And...
我真的很緊張...
I get really stressed out...
好  我會為你獨奏
Okay, I'lI do a solo for you
-怎麼回事  爾尼?  -嘿
-What's up, Ernie? -Hey
史提夫大師出品...
stiffmeister Productions...
還有呢  他只有一顆睪丸
Get this. He has one ball
行為矯正明顯進步
Behavior modification evident
你完蛋了  他媽的
You a dead man, motherfucker
甜心  這是你的
Honey, this Just came for you
那  我先走了
so, I'm going to take off now
和敏感藝術家型的人裡
and sensitive-artist types
嘿  是爾尼垃圾維茲嘛
Hey, it's Ernie Crapowitz
你應該要用這個
You were supposed to use this
JC帶著大夥去
J.C., what, rocking the bunch
帶那婊子回家
Take that bitch home, man
只要你夠帶種
if you think you're man enough
應該更隨性一點
lt should be more spontaneous
基本上就是這樣
That's generally how it works
我真的很抱歉
I'm sorry about your underwear
還有其他所有蠢事
And alI that other shit, too
又是那個醜護士
lt was that fugly nurse again
但我覺得你不一樣
But I think you're different
噢  我想這是你的
Oh, I believe this is yours
你閉嘴好不好?
wilI you cut that out?
你維持了他的傳統
You've continued his legacy
折磨無辜學生...
Tormenting the innocent...
-年輕又大支  -太棒了
-Young and hung. -Great
拿去吧  慢慢享受
There you go. suck on that
史提勒馬上回來
stiffy'lI be back in a Jiffy
戴在我的小雞雞上如何?
and put it on my weenie?
是戴在我頭上  沒錯吧?
It's on my head, right?
你的看來棒極了
Yours look totally fantastic
對  沒錯  我做的
Yeah. That's right. I did
到時候見  混蛋
I'lI see you there, asshole
他後來變得很不錯
And he turned out Just fine
還包括我的運動胸罩
lncluding my training bras
-我得...  -我走了
-I had to... -I gotta go
麥特把電腦關了
Matt turned off the computer
只是請你們幫我去幫伊麗絲
Just help me help Elyse
我們可以靠實力贏的
We could've won on our own
再幫我拿杯思樂冰來
and get me another slushee
但卻給我好靈感
but it gave me a great idea
唉呀呀  真感謝您
Golly, Jeepers, thanks.
當然  這是規定
There are rules, of course
歡迎收看史提勒透視
Welcome to stifler-vision
嘿  史提勒  電話
Hey, stifler. Phone
一   二   三  直線
One, two, three, line
你有兩個姿勢
Now, there are two positions
但你媽可累慘了
But your mom did last night
像他  如果幸運的話
Like him, if we're lucky
放鬆點  你做得很好
Relax. You're doing fine
好久沒看到了
Haven't seen that in a while
山毛櫸完全攻略!
Beechwood licks nuts. Hut!
好  晚餐後過來
Okay, come by after dinner
等等  小心點
Hold on. Be carefuI with it
還有更精彩的呢
And wait tilI you hear this
這個要丟進湖裡
This is going into the lake
別吐我鞋子上  慘啦
Not my shoes. Here we go
沒有你的訂約紀錄
You're not in the book.
但是你快完蛋了
But now, you're going down
收拾一下吧  史提勒
Pack your bags, stifler
-麥擴那裡  -哪裡?
-the Macro. -The what?
-混蛋!  -給我過來
-Bitch! -Get over here
他哪裡都走不了
He ain't going nowhere now
你剛摸了我屁股
You Just touched my bootie
請大家記住...
let's try to remember...
就該這樣
That's what I'm talking about
哈羅  雙D罩杯的雪麗
Hello, Double-D sheree
-沒事吧?  -對
-Are you okay? -Oh, yeah
他快錯過好戲了
Douchebag's gonna miss it
噢  對  那就是我
Hell, yeah. That's me
再坐近一點
sit a little closer, ladies
小子  把瓜帽戴上
Put your beanie on, son
這東西真酷
Dude, this thing is awesome
我發103度的高燒
I've got a fever of 103
-好啊  -發情狗?
-AlI right. -Horn dog?
我知道你在做什麼
I know what you're doing
我沒帶鼓棒來
I don't have my drumsticks
大瀑布正傾瀉
Great Falls laying it down
金屬最讓我興奮了
metaI really turns me on
但他也提到...
But he also says that...
乳頭的泰倫鐵諾
The Tarantino of titties
住手  快住手
stop that. stop that now
祝你順心  蠢貨
Have a great day, fucko
好  儀隊透視
AlI right. Bandee-vision
愚蠢的好男孩...
dorky-ass nice guys...
好  很好
Okay, alI right. AlI right
她們偷我衣服
And they stole my clothes
老兄  我醉死了
I'm fucking fubar, man!
如果可稱作樂曲的話
if you calI that music
好  東大瀑布!
AlI right, Great Falls!
我被下毒了
I've been fucking poisoned
感覺如何? 奧斯卡
How's that feel? Oscar
何況  老實說...
Plus, to be honest...
震動棒耶
It's a dildo. It's a dildo
這是我第一次來
It's my first time here
我們在底特律!
we're in Detroit!
你不知道歌詞
You don't know the words
思樂冰晚會  真的
slushee party. Really
-可能吧  -還我
-Maybe. -Give it back
去吧  混蛋
Go long, you asshole. Go
要是可以你也會的
You would if you could
山毛櫸高校
Beechwood Academy
機器人博士片段
Little bit of Dr. Robot
這封信...
This letter is, well....
小弟  快醒來
Man, big boys, wake up
你的衣服呢?
where are your clothes?
這條牙膏...
And this toothpaste...
將持續追蹤
WilI continue to monitor
我以為布蘭頓贏了
I thought Brandon won
抱歉啦  儀隊們
sorry, bandees
-很好笑  -對
-That's funny. -Yeah
退後  混蛋
step back, bitch
莫札特老天爺!
Holy mother of Mozart
讓比賽開始吧
so let the games begin
我才不來這套
I don't need this shit
-很無聊耶  -好
-I mean lame. -Good
嘿  起司佬...
Hey, cheese dick...
我身上打了六個洞
I have six piercings
丟回來  對
Throw it back. Come on
-柳橙?  -又是柳橙?
-Orange? -Again?
我想要葡萄
I'm feeling grape, dawg
嗨  我是伊麗絲休士頓
Hi. Elyse Houston
到底怎麼回事?
What's going on here?
你好冷酷
That's cold, dawg
他媽的  亞瑞娜
Holy shit, Arrianna
酷斃啦
This is gonna be awesome
東大瀑布高中
East Great Falls High
說得沒錯
Yeah, that's true
大學啦啦隊員喔
College cheerleaders
真夠窘的
This is so embarrassing
好  布蘭頓
Okay, Brandon
我得去看看
Dude, I gotta see this
不  很可愛呢
No, man, it was cute
天  卡住了
Man, the shit's stuck
海盜啊嘿!
Hey, butt pirates ahoy
不會  再見
No, we don't. Bye now
-噢  麥特!  -停
-Oh, Matt! -stop
但這種還是第一次
but this is a first
想得美  怪人
Yeah, right. Freaks
就是合作
is by working together
不能讓你繼續下去
We can't have that
不  是航空...
No it's space....
得做算數喔?
You have to do math?
來比啊  混蛋
suck on that, bitch
他應該刮毛啦
He should shave that
對你是完全正常的
as these things go
除非你讓我觀賞
lf you let me watch
小聲點
Beat it, Jerk off
糟了  慘了
shit, shit, oh, shit
布蘭頓凡德甘普所編
Brandon Vandecamp
你們好嗎?
Hey, what's up, guys?
那是她的音樂
And that's her music
吃屎吧  畢業生
Eat shit, seniors
只是好玩
Oh, it's Just for fun
去找克洛依吧
Let's go find Chloe
有人向我們挑戰
We got a challenge
幹你媽的淫猴
Fucking puss monkey
-對  -別這樣
-Yeah. -stop, man
你還穿蘇格蘭裙
You wore your kilt
辦不到  沒了
I can't. It's gone
你開玩笑吧?
Are you kidding me?
是羅伯茲學校寄的
It's from Robards
東大瀑布高中!
East Great Falls!
等等
Hold it. Hold it. Kids
向左轉
Left flank hut
好  混蛋
Yeah, asshole
看到瓜帽沒?
Notice the beanie?
贏得她們信任?
Earn their trust?
可行喔
Dude, that could work
說到這個
speaking of which,
各位...
Hey, gang...
很酷  大胖?
It's cool. Big O?
然後踏步...
And step, and....
兩個在這...
Two right here...
說他棒極了
said he was amazing
那是什麼?
What is that thing?
你有沒有幫他?
Did you help him?
麗絲  等等  不
Leesy, wait, no
雪曼終結者報告完畢
shermanator out
聖瑪莉山高中!
Mount st. Marie!
這裡的每天
Every day here,
尤  快滾開
Out of my way, yo
我脫褲子
I free ball, ladies
贏得他們的信任
Earn their trust
太娘娘腔了
That's fucking gay
好像你真有需要
Like you need it
就弄傷自己了
and I hurt myself
你跟雙簧管搞的事
porking an oboe
擴音器給我
Give me this thing
右腳走直線
Right foot on line
骯髒的內褲
dirty-girI panties
才不像
No, it doesn't
-麥特?  -麗絲
-Matt? -Leesy
他們在哭嗎?
Are they crying?
對  胸膛間諜
Yeah, spy Chest
山毛櫸高校
Beechwood Academy
好  坐下
Okay, settle down
-待會見  -當然
-Later. -Word
好! 他上鉤了
Yes! We got him
她叫克洛依
Her name is Chloe
右腳踩四
Right foot on four
可以開始了
You're good to go
東大瀑布!
East Great Falls!
四個在這
and four down here
隨要隨有
Delivery on demand
來  丟吧
Come on, throw it
山毛櫸高校
Beechwood Academy
你這混蛋
You son of a bitch
■
狗屎  垃圾
Bullshit, trash
大家好了嗎?
You guys ready?
好喔  對嘛
AlI right. Yeah
房間檢查
Room check, girls
交朋友吧
Make some friends
最討厭了
I hate that
這裡爛透了
This place blows
我有啊
I've got the balls
打錯了  對不起
Missed. sorry
好了  各位
Okay, everybody
這是我的樂團
This is my band
我不同意
I didn't think so
哈羅  麥修
Hello, Matthew
媽的才不要咧
No fucking way
她人似乎很好
she seems nice
是求改變
to make a change
東大瀑布
East Great Falls
來吧!
Come on!
-嘿  -幹嘛?
-Hey. -What?
特別快遞
speciaI delivery
我很享受啊
I am having fun
-對  -爾尼
-Yeah. -Ernie
裡面說什麼?
What's it say?
我有這封信
I have a letter
不放春假
No spring break
搞什麼鬼?
What the fuck?
謝謝  麗絲
Thanks, Leesy
好  你贏了
Fine, you win
晚安
Good night, girls
美麗的小姐
beautifuI lady
哈羅  輸家
Hello, losers
就要狂野
Born to be wild
好熱喔
It's getting hot
山毛櫸獲勝
Beechwood wins
還有日記的事
And the diary
麥特史提勒?
Matt stifler?
真夠爛的
They're so lame
我是混蛋
I am an asshole
噢  抱歉
Oh, I'm sorry
好...
Okay...
珊德絲護士
Nurse sanders
兩位...
Look, kids...
他媽的!
What the fuck!
麥特  別這樣
Matt, don't
哈羅  雙簧管
Hello, oboe
這真酷
This is so cool
那是什麼?
What you got?
-好  -好
-Okay. -Okay
不准打橄欖球
No football
不能畢業
No graduation
很配嘛
suits you well
臀部   臀部
Hips. Hips
噢  天哪!
Oh, my God!
各位...
Hey, guys...
你知道...
You know...
秘密錄影
secret Video
那是什麼?
What is it?
我不...
I don't....
誰吹我?
Who blew me?
儀隊十!
Band 10 hut!
整理房間
Housekeeping
哪個美眉?
What chick?
比劍嗎?
With swords?
我也會
Well, so do l
嘿  奧斯卡
Hey, Oscar
我們真糟
Man, we suck
麥特  麥特
Matt. Matt
嗨  伊麗絲
Hey, Elyse
好  再來
Okay, again
打爛它
Let's kilI it
瘋狂蠢蛋
Crazy fucker
不准開派對
No parties
上不了大學
No college
再轉身
Turn and hut
爛透了
Lame
防曬係數69
s.P.F. 69
厲害吧
suck on that
噢  天哪
Oh, my God
什麼?
What's that?
懂了嗎?
Understand?
哦
AlI right
沒有同校女生
No coeds
懂了嗎?
Comprende?
糟糕了
This is bad
在我這
I have them
你行嗎?
Take that!
對喔
That's right
下回再見
stay tuned
誰想得到?
Who knew?
是假的
It's a fake
可惡!
Holy shit!
超正點
Hell, yeah
羅伊!
L-L-O-Y-D!
好極啦
Hell, yeah
噢  糟了
Oh, shit
我看到了
Yes, I do
五分
Five points
噢  可惡
Oh, shit
真可惡
This sucks
是哦
Yeah, right
丟過來
Right here
不  等等
No. Wait
必卡多?
Picardo?
噢  對了
Oh, yes
史提勒!
stifler!
聽著...
Look...
他慘啦
so busted
聽著...
Look...
沒關係
It's okay
謝謝
Oh, thanks
上床?
Get laid?
噢  對
Oh, yeah
對了!
That's it
嚇死你
Beat that
史提勒!
stifler!
好...
Okay...
可惡
Holy shit
不知好歹
Animals
天哪
Holy shit
漂亮
Good game
抱歉
Excuse me
噢耶!
Oh, yeah
哦...
Well...
過來
Come here
膽小鬼
Pussies
真的?
Really?
算了
Whatever
就知道
Figures
隨便
Whatever
小心
Look out
史提勒
stifler
拿去
Take it
催吐劑
lpecac
事情
at camp
走吧
Be gone
史提非
stiffy
擺臀
Bootie
幹嘛?
What?
什麼?
來
Come on
什麼?
What?
為什麼?
Why?
可惡!
Damn!
對了!
Yes!
好喝
Yummy
別說啦
stop
對!
Yeah!
狗屎
shit
真的
Word
幹
Fuck
好
Good
Fine
好
Okay
sure
再見
Bye
對
Yes
哇
Wow
好
Yes